[THEME MUSIC PLAYING]
[SCREAMING IN PAIN]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
- [ENGINE REVVING]
- [TIRES SCREECHING]
[TIRES SCREECH]
[ENGINES REVVING]
[TRUCK HORN BLARES]
[LOUD CRASH]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
- Stop!
- [GUNSHOTS]
[FIREWORKS EXPLODING]
[METAL RODS CLANGING]
- [ENGINE REVVING]
- [BUS HORN HONKS]
[GLASS SHATTERING]
- [TIRES SCREECHING]
- [LOUD CRASH]
[ENGINES REVVING]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
[GUNSHOTS]
- [TRUCK HORN HONKS]
- [LOUD CRASH]
[TIRES SCREECHING]
We're going to Mr. Chan's.
I'll take care of him myself.
Just have your men
take care of him.
This is easy.
I can handle this!
Sam was in a rush
to go home earlier.
If you're having a hard time
with Ma'am Sam,
you should put more effort
into Ma'am Pia.
I noticed Sam's been really
cranky lately.
She's really eager to solve
this gold smuggling case.
I think she's on to something.
Do it faster!
I want everything out today!
Looks like she didn't drop
Tiger's case.
Yes, I'm here now.
Come inside.
I'll wait for you inside.
I already told her
to keep her hands off it!
You want gold bars? I can
give you gold bars at 70% off.
[GUNSHOTS]
[ROPE ZIPPING ALONG LINE]
[PUNCHES AND KICKS LANDING]
Spread out! We're wiping out
Mr. Chan's men!
[YELLS] Ah!
Come on! Pick up!
- [LINE RINGING]
- [BREATHING HEAVILY]
Where the hell are you guys?!
- [YELLS] Ah!
- [MAGAZINES CLATTER]
Deborah, where is Arturo?
I had him follow Lucas.
What?! Didn't I tell you
to leave Lucas alone?!
Does my word mean nothing
around here anymore?!
I'm just worried.
- [SIGHS SOFTLY]
- [TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
When Victor goes out,
you don't worry like this.
But now with Lucas,
you can't sit still.
Maybe you're the one
who doesn't trust your son.
Mariano.
Victor's freedom rests on
Lucas's shoulders.
If he fails to eliminate
Mr. Chan,
our eldest will rot in prison.
What happens to our business?
- I need a drink.
- [WOMAN] Yes, ma'am.
- Make it a double!
- Coming right up, ma'am.
[GLASSES CLINKING]
Come on! Move!
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
- [SHRIEKS]
- [GLASS SHATTERS]
- Ugh!
- Sorry, ma'am.
[BREATHES DEEPLY]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [GUNSHOT]
- [BLOOD SQUELCHING]
[GRIM MUSIC PLAYING]
[GUNSHOTS]
- [BULLETS SQUELCH INTO FLESH]
- [BODIES THUDDING]
[GUNSHOTS]
[KICKS LANDING]
[RAPID GUNFIRE]
[SLINGSHOT THWACKING]
[THWACKING]
[BLOWS LANDING]
[BODY THUDS]
[GOON] Stop!
- [GUNSHOT]
- [BLOWS LAND]
[GUNSHOTS]
Borromeo, let's split up.
You and Reyes go over there.
Bullet and I will take left.
[RAPID GUNFIRE]
- [KICK LANDS]
- [LOUD CRASH]
[SLINGSHOT THWACKING]
[GUNSHOTS]
- [GRUNTING, GROANING]
- [BLOWS LANDING]
[GUNSHOTS]
[GROANS]
Hey, are you alright?
I'm fine. Let's move!
[GRUNTING]
[BLOWS LANDING]
[SLINGSHOT THWACKING]
- [GUNSHOT]
- [GRUNTS]
[BLOWS LANDING]
[BODY THUDS]
- Hey!
- [THWACKS]
[NUNCHUCKS RATTLING]
[THWACKS]
[METAL WEAPONS CLANGING]
[BODY THUDS]
[BLOWS LANDING]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[NUNCHUCKS RATTLING]
[GUNSHOTS]
NCIA!
[RAPID GUNFIRE]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[KAREN GRUNTS, GROANS]
[GUNFIRE CONTINUES]
[LUCAS] Mr. Chan!
Limbaga, are you alright?
I'm fine. It's nothing fatal.
Let's go!
This way!
Let's hurry!
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[GOON] Drop your weapon.
Drop it!
[NUNCHUCKS RATTLE, CLANG]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
- [GUNSHOTS]
- [BODY THUDS]
[LUCAS GROWLS]
[RAPID GUNFIRE]
Mr. Chan!
NCIA!
Nobody move!
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
- [BLOWS, KICKS LANDING]
- [GABO GROANING]
Argh!
- [OBJECTS CLANK]
- [HEAVY THUD]
- [GOON 1] Get up!
- [GOON 2] Come on!
- [GOON 3] Face us!
- [GOON 4] Let's do this!
[GRUNTS WEAKLY]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[RAPID GUNFIRE]
[FLESH SQUELCHES]
[HEAVY THUD]
[GUNSHOTS]
[GABO GROANS]
[GRUNTS]
- [THWACK]
- [GROANS]
[GABO] Aah!
[THWACKING]
[BODY THUDS]
[KICK LANDS]
[GUNSHOTS]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[KICK LANDS]
- [EXCLAIMS]
- [BODY THUDS]
- [THWACKS]
- [KICK LANDS]
- [THWACKING]
- [GROANING]
[BODY THUDS]
[THRILLING MUSIC PLAYING]
[HEAVY FOOTSTEPS]
Mr. Chan!
[HURRIED FOOTSTEPS]
[STICK CLATTERS]
[SHOES CLACKING]
- [WHISPERS] I've got you.
- [GROANS WEAKLY]
- [RUSHING FOOTSTEPS]
- [GUNSHOTS]
[GUNSHOTS]
[THRILLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[QUICK FOOTSTEPS]
Go, go! Kill them!
[GUNSHOTS]
[MR. CHAN] Men!
We need our car right now!
[THRILLING MUSIC CONTINUES]
[BRASS KNUCKLES SWISH]
[SWITCH CLICKS OFF]
[MR. CHAN] Where's the light?
Where's the light?!
[MUSIC BECOMES SUSPENSEFUL]
- [GUNSHOTS]
- [BLOWS LAND]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[BODY THUDS]
[BLOWS, KICKS LANDING]
[BOXES CLATTERNG]
[RAPID GUNFIRE]
[GUNSHOTS]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[BODIES THUD]
- [BLOWS LANDING]
- [GROANING]
[MR. CHAN] Who are you?!
- [BLOWS LANDING]
- [GROANING]
- [BODY THUDS]
- [GUNSHOTS]
- [BLOWS LANDING]
- [GROANING]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [KICK LANDS]
- [GRUNTS]
[GUNSHOTS]
[BODY THUDS]
[MR. CHAN] Where are you?!
Show yourself!
[GUNSHOTS]
- [BLOWS, KICKS LANDING]
- [GROANING]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[KICK LANDS]
- [GROANS]
- [BODY THUDS]
[EXHALES SHARPLY]
[GROANS]
[RAPID GUNFIRE]
- [BODY THUDS]
- [HURRIED FOOTSTEPS]
[LUCAS] Let's wait for Mr. Chan!
[LAO] We can't do that!
The NCIA agents are here!
- [GUNSHOTS]
- [BODY THUDS]
- Argh!
- Don't let them catch you!
They've got backup coming!
Lee!
- [ENGINES REVVING]
- [TIRES SCREECHING]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[CAR DOOR CLOSES]
[GUNSHOTS]
- Argh...
- Lee, let's go!
[QUICK FOOTSTEPS]
Come on!
Fall back!
[LUCAS GROANS]
Lucas!
- What are you doing here?
- He got shot!
Who shot Lucas?!
That NCIA agent!
Samantha Jacinto!
- [TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [GUNSHOTS]
Get Lucas to safety!
[RAPID GUNFIRE]
- [LAO] Let's go!
- Get in!
[CAR DOORS OPEN, CLOSE]
[ENGINES REVVING]
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
- [SWITCH CLICKS ON]
- [POWER HUMMING]
[HEAVY FOOTSTEPS]
Freeze!
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Don't move!
[GUNSHOT]
Mr. Chan, you are under arrest.
You have the right
to remain silent.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[FOOTSTEPS APROACHING]
Team!
Ma'am, he's the key to getting
Victor Zafra convicted.
And because you caught
Mr. Chan,
your reputation will finally
be restored.
[DRAMATIC MUSIC PLAYING]
Lucas?!
- Sir, it's Lucas!
- [DOOR OPENS]
He got shot!
God, what happened?!
- Go and bring him upstairs.
- Arturo,
- call the doctor!
- I already did, Ma'am.
They're on the way here.
[DOOR CLOSES]
[LUCAS GROANING IN PAIN]
- Ow!
- Lucas!
- Careful.
- Lucas, god!
- Ow...
Here, let me help you.
- Hold on!
- Ow, Ma! It hurts!
- Sorry!
- [GROANING CONTINUES]
Wait. Let's see how bad it is.
Lucas, were you able
to get rid of Mr. Chan?
[DEBORAH] Who shot you?
Ma'am, Sir, Doc Alain is here.
- [GROANING CONTINUES]
- Excuse me.
- [DEBORAH] He's here.
- Excuse me, please.
Doc.
- Please excuse me.
- Be careful!
- I'm sorry for this.
- Do be careful.
[GROANING CONTINUES]
[DEBORAH] Is he okay?
I'll take it from here.
Please give us some space.
Alright. Lay down for a bit.
[GROANING IN PAIN]
- [SQUELCHES]
- [DOOR OPENS]
[GRIM MUSIC PLAYING]
[DOOR CLOSES]
- Ma'am, I'm sorry--
- Imbecile!
Didn't I entrust Lucas to you?
Huh?!
Ma'am, Lucas was already shot--
Because you were too slow!
If only you were quicker,
you would have saved him!
You could have saved him!
- Ma'am!
- Useless!
- [MARIANO] That's enough!
- [BLOW LANDS]
- [THUDS]
- [MARIANO] Enough.
It should have been you!
I said, enough!
- [GUNSHOTS]
- [DEBORAH GRUNTS]
- Let go of me!
- Give me that!
Calm down!
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
- [MR. CHAN] No! Don't touch me!
- [CASTOR] Shut up!
[MR. CHAN] Call my lawyer!
I'll call my lawyer!
- Let me go!
- What now, ma'am?
We won't be able to keep
this from Sir Delgado.
I think he'll be pleased
with this anyway.
- Sam!
- What the?
So you guys did go to Mr. Chan.
[SEBASTIAN] Huh?
Are you guys alright?
Bring Karen to the clinic.
Get yourselves checked too.
- Go on.
- Mm-hmm.
Karen, what happened?
Were you shot?
[SARCASTICALLY] You noticed?
You're right on target.
You shot my heart too.
Want me to shoot you for real?
[CLICKS TONGUE] Sam,
[GRUNTS]
you know I could have
helped you.
I wish you told me about it.
Look at what happened to them!
What's important is we captured
Mr. Chan.
- Let's go.
- Jacinto.
What is the meaning of this?
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Sir, there was just a bit
of trouble.
But we finally got Mr. Chan.
Aren't you supposed to be
hands off from the case?
Don't you understand
what it means?!
I'm just doing my job.
Jacinto, your job
is to honor my commands.
Sebastian, take care
of Mr. Chan.
Sam.
- [SEBASTIAN] Sir.
- [MR. CHAN] Impossible!
In my office, now!
- [SEBASTIAN] This way.
- [MR. CHAN] Let me go!
- Let me go!
- Stop struggling!
- My lawyer! I need my lawyer!
- Come on, follow us.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
What did really happen?
Boss, when we arrived
at Mr. Chan's warehouse,
we immediately attacked
his group.
But suddenly, a group
of NCIA agents arrived.
We had to engage with them.
We're not sure if the police
we encountered
are Mr. Chan's men.
It's like they knew
we were coming.
[SCOFFS]
Leave.
You...
all reek of incompetence!
Get out of my face!
Get out.
Get out!
Out!
[BREATHING HEAVILY]
[MOROSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[DOOR SLAMS CLOSE]
You didn't follow my orders.
You didn't follow the protocol!
Sir, I can't stand just
lounging around in the office
doing nothing!
All while those involved
in the gold smuggling case
is roaming around freely!
You're no longer handling
the gold smuggling case!
What did I tell you, huh?
You are hands off on this case!
Why did you disobey me?
What do you want to prove?
That I can solve this case.
No, Sam.
You've proven
how stubborn you are!
that you don't listen
to those who are above you!
And you even dragged
your colleagues into this.
You know what, Sam,
I was already working on
not getting you suspended
because of Pia's report.
But because
of what you've done...
But because of what
all of you have done,
you won't just get a suspension,
you and your whole team might
get dismissed from service!
Sir, wait a minute.
Please don't involve
the whole team.
I encouraged them
to work with me on this.
If there's someone to blame,
then let it be me.
[DELGADO SIGHS]
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
Sam.
Do you know that
I see you as my own daughter?
But do you know what, Sam,
just how painful
was your disobedience?
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
Oh, sir?
I know what we did was wrong
but we did it anyways.
I'm sorry.
I knew I have my own mistakes
and shortcomings.
But whatever you decide
on, I'll accept it.
But please just punish me.
Not the whole team.
[TENSE MUSIC CONTINUES]
[MOTORCYCLE ENGINE REVVING]
[ENGINE STOPS]
[INTRIGUING MUSIC PLAYING]
- He brought it home?
- Mm-hmm.
I knew it.
[KEYS JANGLING]
[DOOR OPENS]
[DOOR CREAKS, CLOSES]
[SCOFFS]
Gabo can't really be trusted.
[LINE RINGING]
[PHONE RINGING]
- Hello?
- [UWAK] Omeng.
Gabo is here.
He has the gold.
He brought it inside his house.
Why?
Lawin just called.
It's about Gabo...
he ran away with the gold.
[TENSE MUSIC PLAYING]
[LUGGAGE CLICKS]
[SNICKERS]
Gabo wouldn't do that.
I know him well.
It's too soon to tell.
Let's not judge him yet.
[SUSPENSEFUL MUSIC PLAYING]
[MUSIC TURNS SOMBER]
[BETCHAY] Time is running out
for your father.
Pa!
It's not like your father
expects anything of you either.
Pa!
[BETCHAY]
Money! We need money!
[SOMBER MUSIC CONTINUES]
Gabo isn't really to be trusted.
He ran away with the gold.
What do we do now?
I'm not going to get back
at Mr. Chan, Ma.
But to the person who shot me!
I'll make Samantha Jacinto pay.
Talking won't work
on Ricardo anymore.
We need to negotiate
the hard way.
Someone was there
that's why we caught
Mr. Chan easily.
Could it be the same mystery man
who helped us catch Tiger?
The question is, who is he?
You know how his mind works.
He's from Ginintuang Lupa
after all.
I have the money
for Papa's surgery.
I won't let anything bad
happen to my father.
I'll do everything
to keep him alive.
Where did you get the money?
What kind of job? Was it legal?
He'll be easily tempted.
With that much gold, for sure,
he was blinded by greed.